

PROFILE

Passionate about food and wine, I used to organize wine-tasting events for a family business while doing odd jobs on the side. I wanted to use my creativity by writing blog articles about our products with Wordpress.

Then, I discovered a passion for web development and wanted to deepen my knowledges. I thus took the courses at Le Wagon, which was an amazing experience to improve my IT skills.

Now I'm working hard to upgrade my wine e-shop and find a job as a Junior Developer.

INFOS

Age: 34

PHONE: +32 468 12 98 90

ADDRESS: Rue notre-dame, 21 Bte B5

1420 Braine l'Alleud

E-MAIL:

sebternest@hotmail.com

LINKEDIN:

linkedin.com/in/sebastienternest

PORTFOLIO

https://sebt-max.github.io/

GITHUB PROFILE:

https://github.com/sebT-max

HOBBIES

Cooking, oenology, guitar

SÉBASTIEN TERNEST

Junior Web Developer

EXPERIENCE

Les Epicurieux de Bacchus - Event coordinator January 2016 - now

Website development with Wordpress - emailing - flyers with Adobe Photoshop.

Start-up Veojobs - Product manager March 2015 - November 2015

- Organization and promotion of job days via Veojobs App.
- Organization of remote-interviews via the same application.
- Curriculum analysis and contact with candidates and companies.
- Content writing

IBS Benelux - Digital marketing (internship) March 2014 - June 2014

- Negotiating, monitoring, reporting, planning, developing and implementing short-term and long-term social media strategies.
- Selling websites on the phone.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon-Brussels

September 2020 - February 2021

24-week intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, SQL, git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails. Designed, implemented and shipped to production a clone of AirBnB and a Rails prototype (syllabuy.be)

ICHEC Brussels

February - June 2015

125 hours of e-marketing courses: emailing, crowdfunding, Linkedin, Facebook, Pinterest, monitoring, SEO, SEA, data privacy, e-branding and reputation.

SKILLS

Ruby-on Rails: Advanced | HTML5: Advanced | CSS3: Advanced | Wordpress: Advanced | Bootstrap: Advanced | JS ES6: Intermediate

Languages

French (native) | English (C1+) | Dutch(B2) | Spanish (B2+)